Hudson River Conservation Society, Inc. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 2. Scrapbooks, 1939 - 1959; 2; 5 linear foot 56 - 61 772 - 781
  - Scrapbook 5 - Homes in Rockland County Threatened by the Thruway (Folder 776, Box 59)
  - Report on the Eastern Highlands - 1941 (Folder 777, Box 60)
  - Scrapbook 1 1939 - 1947 (Folder 778, Box 61)
  - Scrapbook 2 1948 - 1957 (Folder 779, Box 61)
  - Scrapbook 3 1955 - 1959 (Folder 780, Box 61)
  - Scrapbook 4 1958 - 1959 (Folder 781, Box 61)